Guide to the Yale University Corporation 2012 Presidential Search Committee Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Corporation 2012 Presidential Search Committee records
2012-2012
RU 1126
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.25
(2 boxes)
The records consist of materials created during Yale's 2012 presidential search.
Yale Corporation
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of materials created during Yale's 2012 presidential search.
General
Forms part of Yale Record Group 1-B (YRG 1-B), Records of Yale Corporation committees.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Office of the President, 2013 and 2014.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
College presidents; Salovey, Peter; Yale University -- Presidents -- Selection and appointment; Yale Corporation
- Records, 2012; Accession 2014-A-015
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 1, 2088.
  - General Search Files
    - Arrangement of Presidential Search According to Search Firm, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Community Memorandums, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Community Message Richard Levin Resignation, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Constituent Outreach, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
    - News Articles on Presidential Search, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Search Statement, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Presidential Search Statement on Operating Practices and Confidentiality, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Review of Critical Attributes, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Search Committee Outreach List, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Search Procedural Advice from Elsewhere, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      General
      Folder 14 has been returned permanently to the Office of the President.
  - Candidate Files
    - Candidates A List, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Candidates A List Related Documents, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 28-30)
    - Candidates B List Related Documents, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
    - Candidates C List Related Documents, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 33-35)
    - Candidate List, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Candidates Files Nominations and Recommendations
    - Clinton, Hillary Rodham, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Clinton, William Jefferson, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Additional material, Accession 2014-A-063
  - Notes on the Corporation's involvement and meeting process, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Presidential search summary report and corresponding attachments, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)